

CONTACT

নুঠী 27 Allée Daniel Lavallée 76000, Rouen

+33 7 66 29 08 12

bessa460@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/younesbessa

github.com/YounesBessa

younesbessa.com

LANGUAGES

French Native language

English
Fluent (C1 level)

Certificate: Cambridge English Advanced

German

Arabic Conversational (B2 Level)

SKILLS

•••• React

••• TypeScript

••• Next

••• MongoDB

••• GraphQL

••• Symfony

YOUNES BESSA 23 YEARS OLD

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a 23-year-old Junior full stack Web developer from France. I study web development at Need for School in Rouen.

I'm an apprentice at <u>Expat's Facilities</u> and I'm also part of an association called <u>onRuntime Studio</u>.

I particularly like to meet new and diverse people and work with modern frontend tools and frameworks like React.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer (2 month internship, then apprenticeship)

Expat's Facilities, Rouen | August 2021 - Present

Tech stack: MongoDB, Apollo, Next, GraphQL, Express, Node

Rhythm of the apprenticeship: 1 week at school / 2 weeks at the company

Web Developer (two month internship)

Rouen Informatique, Rouen | April 2021 - June 2021

I designed internal digital tools related to the CRM of the company at the request of the internship supervisor and in compliance with the deadlines.

I analysed the needs and developed all the technical functionalities of these tools. I solved the problems and fixed the bugs detected by the internship supervisor.

Languages: HTML,CSS,PHP,SQL,JS Libraries: libcurl(PHP), jQuery

APIs: Google Maps API (JavaScript), Axonaut API

Framework: Bootstrap CMS: WordPress

EDUCATION

Need for School | Web development | Rouen, France

October 2020 - 2023

Bachelor's Degree

- Apprenticeship
- · Learning how to use frameworks and languages
- Learning by doing
- Project-oriented pedagogy
- Working in groups (3 to 5 members each)

University of Rouen

First and second year in French law | 2018 - February 2020

University of Rouen

First year in Economic and Social Administration | 2017 - 2018

French baccalaureate (Economics branch)

French International School, Riyadh | 2017